mindviz.com 2016-04-11

# MindViz - Your Friends, Photos, Videos, Music, Forums, Chat & More!

**MindViz Privacy Policy**

The MindViz Network ("MVIZ"), comprised of the Internet sites [mindviz.com](http://mindviz.com/), [adlogic.mindviz.com](http://adlogic.mindviz.com/), [mail.mindviz.com](http://mail.mindviz.com/), [mvhosted.com](http://mvhosted.com/), [mvtracker.com](http://mvtracker.com/), [ai-buddy.com](http://ai-buddy.com/), [poetictimes.com](http://poetictimes.com/), [awayhunter.com](http://awayhunter.com/), [profilehunter.com](http://profilehunter.com/), [poetsbest.com](http://poetsbest.com/), [awayhell.com](http://awayhell.com/), [pokerhell.com](http://pokerhell.com/), [aimprank.com](http://aimprank.com/), [picsfolio.com](http://picsfolio.com/), [journalhell.com](http://journalhell.com/), [mylinkbox.com](http://mylinkbox.com/), [forumhell.com](http://forumhell.com/), [audiohell.com](http://audiohell.com/), [avatarhell.com](http://avatarhell.com/), [iconhell.com](http://iconhell.com/), [blinkyhell.com](http://blinkyhell.com/), [dollhell.com](http://dollhell.com/), [12gracestreet.com](http://12gracestreet.com/), and [metashark.com](http://metashark.com/) (the "MVIZ Sites"), is committed to protecting the privacy of users of the MVIZ Sites. At MVIZ, we intend to give you as much control as possible over your personal information, including registration data. As part of the normal operation of the MVIZ Sites, we collect information from you. This Privacy Statement describes the information we collect about you and how that information may be used. 

**Information Gathered through the MVIZ Sites:**

MVIZ will track the domains from which people visit the MVIZ Sites in order to gain aggregate data that may be analyzed for trends and statistics. Subject to the provisions of this Privacy Statement, MVIZ may use accumulated aggregate data for several purposes including, but not limited to, marketing analysis, evaluation of MVIZ's services, and business planning. 

Currently, MVIZ uses personal information as a basis for notifications to users, and in order to implement the Terms and Conditions of Use governing the MVIZ Sites (the "Terms"). Generally, the user names, email addresses, and any additional information that a user may choose to post are publicly available on the MVIZ Sites.  When users voluntarily and publicly disclose personal information that may contain Registration Data, as defined in the Terms, or otherwise post personal information in conjunction with content subject to a license, such personal information necessarily will be disclosed subject to the terms of the applicable license. An example of such a disclosure includes, but is not limited to, a user's disclosure of personal information as part of a message posted to a public message forum. 

MVIZ may conduct surveys or other studies of its user base and usage for marketing and planning purposes. Participation in such surveys is at the user's option, but MVIZ does reserve the right to conduct mandatory surveys in the future. With respect to information collected from such surveys or studies, and in the event that responses are to be publicly disclosed, users will be notified at the time they take the survey and MVIZ will disclose only aggregate information regarding its users and not personal information identifying any specific individual. Notwithstanding the foregoing, in cases where surveys allow users to submit written comments, and where MVIZ advises users of the possibility of such disclosure at the time they take the survey, MVIZ reserves the right to disclose text information provided by any user through such a survey, provided that no personal information identifying that user is disclosed.  Circumstances under which MVIZ would publicly disclose aggregate information include, but are not limited to, sharing survey results with the site population, providing data to MVIZ advertisers on user preferences and/or demographics, business planning, and publicizing overall usage data in press communications. 

_Cookies_ : MVIZ employs "cookies" to provide users with tailored information. A "cookie" is an element of data that a website, when visited by a user, sends to that user's browser which, in turn, may store that element on the user's hard drive or memory.  MVIZ uses cookies to better serve users of our MVIZ Sites; any cookies sent by MVIZ will be marked so that they will be accessible only by MVIZ Sites subject to this Privacy Statement. However, at his or her option and at his or her sole expense and responsibility, any user may block or delete our cookies from his or her hard drive. However, by disabling cookies, certain site features and functionality may no longer work properly, or at all. 

_Other Notification_ : In order to implement or enforce the Terms, MVIZ may use user-provided e-mail addresses to contact users on an individual basis.  At no time, unless such disclosure is required by law, a governmental agency, or specifically authorized by the user, will MVIZ disclose individual user personal information to unrelated third parties that is not publicly available. 

**Links with other sites**

The MVIZ Sites contain links to other websites, whether owned or controlled by MVIZ affiliates, or unrelated third parties. Please note that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from those of the MVIZ Sites. MVIZ is not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of any linked website. We encourage you to read the privacy statement of any website you may visit. 

**3rd Party Advertisers**

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [www.networkadvertising.org](http://networkadvertising.org/). 

**Choice**

_"Opt-in" Emails_ : Users may "opt-in" to receive site notifications, newsletters, or other information via email. Users may remove themselves from such services at their discretion. Any email sent to an "opt-in" list will include directions for how a user may remove himself or herself from the list, or a URL where the user may find such directions. 

_Co-Registration_ : Users may "opt-in" to register for or receive offers from third-parties via the co-registration offers provided within our member registration process. Users may remove themselves from such services at their discretion. Any email sent to an "opt-in" list should include directions for how a user may remove himself or herself from the list, or a URL where the user may find such directions. Unfortunately these services are provided by third parties and MVIZ has no control over those services ( they are not owned or operated by MVIZ ). 

_Profile Display_ : In some cases, users' personal information may be publicly available through a user's profile display. In such cases, users have the option to opt out of publicly displaying their personal information, including e-mail addresses.  Users may also enlist this technique when posting comments on certain MVIZ Sites.  In cases where site profiles allow users to display optional information publicly, such entry and display is at the user's discretion and may be changed at any time by the user. 

_Email Display_ : In some cases, users may have the opportunity to use an MVIZ Site to send electronic mail to another user or email list. In such cases, a user's valid email address and real name will be included with such messages. In order to prevent abuse, users may not opt-out of such a display, but may choose to refrain from using such MVIZ Site to transmit an email message. 

**Access**

On certain MVIZ Sites, users can view their data on their personal profile page. When technically feasible, users are permitted to update their personal information directly through MVIZ. When such updating service is not technically feasible, MVIZ will make reasonable efforts to assist users in updating their personal information. 

**Security**

To secure site integrity, MVIZ employs measures, including but not limited to security audits, use of encryption tools and software, and other reasonable security measures and procedures. 

Internal access to users' private and nonpublic personal information is restricted to site administrators and individuals on a need-to-know basis. 

**Enforcement**

In the event that MVIZ becomes aware that site security is compromised or nonpublic user information has been disclosed to unrelated third parties as a result of external activity, including but not limited to external security attacks, MVIZ shall take reasonable measures which it deems appropriate, including but not limited to internal investigation and reporting, and notification to and cooperation with law enforcement authorities, notwithstanding other provisions of this Privacy Statement. 

If MVIZ becomes aware that a user's personal information provided to MVIZ has been disclosed in a manner not in accordance with this Privacy Statement, MVIZ shall make reasonable efforts to notify the affected user, as soon as reasonably possible and as permitted by law, of what information has been disclosed, to the extent that MVIZ knows this information. 

**Updates to the Privacy Statement**

To update the Privacy Statement, we will post both the changed version and its effective date at <http://mindviz.com/privacy.php>. 

**No Guarantees For Factors Beyond MVIZ's Control**

**While this Privacy Statement expresses MVIZ's standards for maintenance of private data, it is not in a position to guarantee that the standards will always be met. There may be factors beyond MVIZ's control (e.g., "script kiddies", "crackers and other malcontents") that may result in disclosure of data. As a consequence, MVIZ disclaims any warranties or representations relating to maintenance or nondisclosure of private information.**

**Last modified: October 1st, 2004**
